[
    {
        "question": "كت ويليام",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ايرين",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت همتارو",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت الويفيا",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت رايلي",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ال",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت لاو",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت يوريتشي",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت توبي",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت نوبارا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ليفاي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت هاشيراما",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت بوروتو",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت يوسوب",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ريم",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت اوتشيها شيسوي",
        "response": "اوتشيها شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت كيد",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ميكاسا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت دانزو",
        "response": "دانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت وينغ",
        "response": "وينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت تينشيهان",
        "response": "تينشيهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت بيكوهان",
        "response": "بيكوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت كازيكاجي",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت جيرايا",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت كوكومي",
        "response": "كوكومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت غيو",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت تشيو",
        "response": "تشيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ساسوري",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت نيزوكو",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ميدوريا",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت نيجي",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ليزا",
        "response": "ليزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت كاغويا",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت هينا",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت الوكا",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت هيناتا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت زينتسو",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت رينغوكو",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت كورتا",
        "response": "كورتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت هيسوكا",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت انوس",
        "response": "انوس"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت بياكوغان",
        "response": "بياكوغان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت شوكو",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ديكو",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت يامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت فانجانس",
        "response": "فانجانس"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت يوليوس",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت تسوموغو",
        "response": "تسوموغو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت نانامي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ايزن",
        "response": "ايزن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت زاراكي",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت اوراهارا",
        "response": "اوراهارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت اينوي",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت غوهان",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت كيريلين",
        "response": "كيريلين"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت هيناتسورو",
        "response": "هيناتسورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كت ريتشيل",
        "response": "ريتشيل"
    }
]